[{"answer": "Sounds like a good time.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Thoughts?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "It was pretty exciting, you know, because, you know, all of us grew up here.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What was -- when you first played here, what was the experience like to you?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "I -- there's a picture somewhere of that, where it's sold out, Friday, Saturday and Sunday, and how much bigger do you get than that?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Let me see, I remember back when The Byrds played here, The Doors played here, all that stuff.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Does it not bring back quite the happy memories it does for the others?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "You know, like it was like a dream come true.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "And what was it like to realize that dream?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I think we're very lucky.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I'm 48.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Oh, you're 49?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "No, I'm 60.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "You're 50?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "You're 49, right?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "You look at Mick Jagger and think, he's still bouncing around in his 60s, so can we?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes, disgracefully.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Just grow old disgracefully?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I think we just had fun.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Is it all it's cracked up to be, when you look back, do you wish you'd been slightly more temperate?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I was selling light bulbs.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What were you doing, Nikki?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I was painting houses.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What were you doing?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I was repairing motorcycles.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Mick?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Amazing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "-- would you agree with the rest of his assessment?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I think -- I grew up in Idaho and I always looked up to these bands like Aerosmith and Kiss and the Stones.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Nikki, you've been nerdy, though, haven't you?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "That's a pretty good overall description.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How do you answer to that charge?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "You know, that, I don't know -- I don't know about that.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Unpredictable?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, I think Ozzie did win in the end.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Who was the bigger hellraiser?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, when she would leave, he would ride on our tour bus with us.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What were -- what were you doing?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Ozzie?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I can't remember -- I think one or two of you recently described a kind of average day at the height of Motley Crue mania, when you were in the party phase, and it was just utterly compelling, every detail was compelling.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Like, you know, how do you top that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "It was just -- it was just one big day.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How would it go?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "First thing you do, yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "First thing you do?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "EE: We thought it was.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Was it a good idea?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Actually, I think it only happened once.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "How many times did you do this?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "There's -- no, that's what we were like.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "No real need to inject it?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "It drips down the back of your throat.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Did it taste any better coming through your veins?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Just at the gig, you know --", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Then what happens?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "The boyfriends would say no.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Did you ever get rejected?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "It's kind of everything.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What sort of drugs are knocking around there?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, yes --", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Remember the bottle caps?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Terrible.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "How could I not (INAUDIBLE) what was going on?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Yes, two hours.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Now, the gig ends, you've got a two-hour -- two-hour show, on average?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, it was like the different -- we had the shower rooms.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What happens back -- is it -- is it sort of heinous backstage, as I always imagined?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "You know, we just -- it would just be -- it would just be, you know, girls and drug dealers and just alcohol --", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Clarify?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "There was always enough.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How many women are backstage?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes, he always -- he always took more.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "You'd take six?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "And that's what the audience was in for the same thing.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "To be the most excessive band ever?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I occasionally drink.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Do any of you still drink?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "No drugs anymore?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yes, I -- (CROSSTALK)", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "So you've cleaned up, basically?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "It's a bit sad.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Isn't it sad, really?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I mean for me, it just quit working and it just started to go the other way.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Do you feel sad or is it like one of those things that eventually, that's it?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "You nearly died, didn't you?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "You know, I went to rehab.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "But what was the moment for you when you finally kicked heroin, because it's a notoriously hard drug, you know, to get rid of?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "You know, actually, it's more of an inconvenience than anything else for me, because it's like, you know, standing up straight is -- is real tough for me, because -- just to make a long story short, when I'm on stage, this is the most -- worst part, walking into things.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "This arthritis that you have -- how does that affect your life?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Walking into microphones, walking into the -- to the drum riser, walking into like sets, things that I want to see on stage that move and do kind of things are like I can't see it.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Yes, you do.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "I sound like a doctor, huh?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "-- because it's a chronic condition, isn't it?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, as a father, you know, you want to be there to protect your children and -- and do whatever you can to keep them safe.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Did that change everything for you?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "And you knew that, did you?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "SkylarNeil.org.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "If people want to donate money, how do they do that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "As simple as that?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Tommy, you've got two children, two boys?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Fifteen and almost 14.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "How old are they now?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- it's awesome.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "And what's it like for you being a dad with two young teenage sons?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How do you think -- how are you going to deal with that?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I've done...", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "How do you deal with it, in terms of advice you give to your offspring?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "You've got four kids, right, don't you?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I have a 20 -year-old, I have a 17 -year-old, a 16 -year- old and a 10 -year-old.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "And have you gotten where you've had to do that?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "You know, I just try to share with them my experience.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Then what do you say?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Geez.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Want to -- want to -- want to try a number out there?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "I'm not -- I'm not touching this one.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Where are we headed?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "I don't think we've ever even really talked about it, have we?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Like Vince said, 50 percent twice is how much?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "You know, I'm really happy in a relationship right now.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Who's the woman?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Yes, it would be her.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "It would be her?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "The current lady in your life?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "The same.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Tommy?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "The same.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Mick?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "No, in Vegas.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "In LA?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "In Vegas?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "I think you just learn by your mistakes, you know, and don't really regret them.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Any regrets?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "I think we've, you know, we've known each other longer than anybody else besides our parents and -- and -- and brothers and sisters.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "How have you managed to keep this kind of relationship with each other, which seems very good?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "We're going to know.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "But you'll know that moment?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "Wow, man.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 810, "question": "What was the -- what was the greatest night of them all, the one -- if you could have a party tonight, you'd have again, what was the one?", "qSentId": 809}, {"answer": "I remember that.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "I could have said any city in the world, couldn't I?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "Got lucky, yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 832, "question": "Well, I managed -- I got lucky there, right?", "qSentId": 831}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "You've never done this before, right?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "So it's -- it's a perfect fit for us.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 858, "question": "Well, it's so Vegas, isn't it?", "qSentId": 857}, {"answer": "It's starting on February 3rd and we're going to be...", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "When -- when -- when is it happening?", "qSentId": 861}, {"answer": "We go to -- we, you, everybody --", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "How do you get tickets?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Are you -- are you planning the mother of all shows?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 880, "question": "Is this going to be the biggest extravaganza?", "qSentId": 879}, {"answer": "You know, I think that we're getting to that place where -- I mean, I know I've been writing.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "Another album on the way?", "qSentId": 891}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I -- I think, you know, with -- with this band, you know, it's just kind of like, you know, we did it our way.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 911, "question": "If you could write your own epitaph?", "qSentId": 910}, {"answer": "The palest guy in rock and roll.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "Mick?", "qSentId": 915}, {"answer": "Oh, God, I don't know.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 921, "question": "Tommy?", "qSentId": 920}, {"answer": "Let's go.", "docId": "111202pmt", "aSentId": 938, "question": "Shall we one more for the road?", "qSentId": 937}]